By now, you've had a lot of practice with data processing and with defining RNNs.
你已经掌握了很多数据处理和 RNN 实践经验
So, I'm not going to give you too much guidance here,
所以对于这个模型的定义
when it comes to defining this model.
我就不废话那么多了
Here's what it should look like generally.
只说说大概流程
The model should be able to take in our word tokens,
模型将接受字词标记
and the first thing that these go through will be an embedding layer.
这些标记首先会进入嵌入层
We have about 74,000 different words,
数据集大约有 74,000 个不同字词
and so this layer is going to be responsible for converting our word tokens,
这一层负责将整数字词标记
our integers into embeddings of a specific size.
转换为特定大小的嵌入向量
Now, you could train a Word2Vec model separately,
我们可以单独训练 Word2Vec 模型
and actually just use the learned word embeddings as input to an LSTM.
并将学习到的字词嵌入当做输入传入 LSTM 层
But it turns out that these embedding layers are still useful even if
虽然这些嵌入层没有接受训练
they haven't been trained to learn the semantic relationships between words.
并学习字词之间的语义关系
So in this case, what we're mainly using
但是这些嵌入层也很有用
this embedding layer for is dimensionality reduction.
这个嵌入层主要用于降维
It will learn to look at our large vocabulary and map
它将查看庞大的词汇表
each word into a vector of a specified embedding dimension.
并将每个字词映射到具有指定嵌入维度的向量
Then, after our embedding layer,
在嵌入层之后
we have an LSTM layer.
是 LSTM 层
This is defined by a hidden state size and number of layers as you know.
LSTM 层由隐藏状态大小和层级数量进行定义
At each step, these LSTM cells will produce an output and a new hidden state.
在每一步 这些 LSTM 单元将生成输出和新的隐藏状态
The hidden state will be passed to the next cell as input,
隐藏状态将当做输入传入下个单元
and this is how we represent a memory in this model.
这就是模型的记忆方式
The output is going to be fed into a Sigmoid activated fully connected output layer.
输出将传入 S 型激活函数全连接输出层
This layer will be responsible for mapping
此层级将负责
the LSTM layer outputs to a desired output size.
将 LSTM 层输出映射到期望的输出大小
In this case, this should be the number of our sentiment classes, positive or negative.
即情感类别“positive”或“negative”的数量
Then, the Sigmoid activation function is responsible for
S 型激活函数负责
turning all of those outputs into a value between zero and one.
将所有这些输出转换为 0-1 之间的值
This is the range we expect for our encoded sentiment labels.
这是我们期望的编码情感标签的范围
Zero is a negative and one is a positive review.
0 表示 negative 1 表示 positive
So, this model is going to look at a sequence of words that make up a review.
模型将查看构成影评的字词序列
Here, we're interested in only the last Sigmoid output because this will
但是我们只关心最后的 S 型函数输出
produce the one label we're looking for at
因为该层级将在模型处理完
the end of processing a sequence of words in a review.
影评中的字词序序列后生成 1 个标签
So here's a little more explanation and some links to documentation if you need it.
这部分是解释说明和参考文档
Then below, in this first cell,
在下面的第一个单元格中
I'm going to check if a GPU is available for training.
我将检查是否有可供训练模型的 GPU
Then here, I want you to complete this model.
请在这里完成该模型
It should take in all these parameters: our vocab size,
它包含以下参数
output size, embedding dimension,
vocab 大小、输出大小、嵌入维度
hidden dimension, number of layers,
隐藏维度、层级数量
and an optional dropout probability,
以及可选的丢弃概率
and create an entire sentiment RNN model.
并创建完整的情感分析 RNN 模型
You'll be responsible for completing the init and forward functions for this model.
你需要完成 init 和 forward 函数
Remember that the output should just be the last value from our Sigmoid output layer.
注意 输出只能是 S 型输出层的最后一个值
I'll also ask you to complete the init hidden function for the LSTM layer.
请完成 LSTM 层级的 init 隐藏函数
This should initialize the hidden and cell state to be
它应该将隐藏状态和单元状态全初始化为 0
all zeros and move them to a GPU, if available.
并将它们移到 GPU 上（如果有的话）
I'd encourage you to look at the documentation when helpful or your other code examples.
建议查阅文档或参考其他代码示例
You should have all the information you need to complete this model on your own.
你已经掌握了所有必要知识 能够自己完成这个模型了
If you're confident in your model definition, later in this code,
如果你对模型定义很有信心
you'll be able to define your model hyperparameters and train it.
之后就可以定义模型参数并训练模型啦
Next, I'll show you one solution for defining the sentiment RNN model.
接下来我将演示如何定义情感分析 RNN 模型
But I do think this is a fun task to try out on your own in earnest too.
这个任务很有趣 记得自己尝试一下哟
I think it's a great exercise in thinking about how
这道练习可以促使你思考
data is shaped as it moves through a model. So, good luck.
数据经过模型时是如何变形的加油！